A Finding Aid to the Wilbur H. Burnham Studios Records, circa 1904-1991, in the Archives of American Art AAA.wilbhbur
Archives of American Art
- Project Files, 1916-1980s; Series 6; 10.6 Linear feet Boxes 2-12, 42
  - Washington D. C., Washington Cathedral (Box 11)
    - Baptistry Windows, 1950s (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Book of Common Prayer Window, 1940s (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Clerestory Windows, 1940s-1950s (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - James Sheldon Correspondence, 1930s-1940s (Box 11, Folder 9-13)
    - Joan of Arc Panel, 1940s-1960s (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Lee Jackson Windows, 1950s (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - North Transept, 1940s-1960s (Box 11, Folder 16-17)
    - North Wall Great Choir Windows, 1940s (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Rose and Lancet Windows, 1950s-1960s (Box 11, Folder 19-20)
    - Stair Well Windows, 1940s-1950s (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Sayre Memorial, 1950s-1960s (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Worcester Windows, 1950s (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Washington, GA, First United Methodist Church, 1950s-1960s (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Waterbury, CO, Bunker Hill Congregational Church, 1940s-1960s (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Watertown, CO, Christ Church, 1930s-1940s (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Watertown, MA, Union Church, 1950s (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Webster, MA, Church of the Reconciliation, 1920s-1960s (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Webster Groves, MO, Webster Hills United Methodist Church, 1950s-1970s (Box 11, Folder 29-31)
  - Wellesley, MA, Saint Andrew's Church, 1950s-1960s (Box 12, Folder 1-2)
  - West Columbia, TX, Saint Mary's Episcopal Church, 1950s (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - West Haven, CO, Christ Church Parish, 1940s-1970s (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - West Lynn, MA, Sacred Heart Church, 1940s (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - West Roxbury, MA, Holy Name Church, 1920s-1940s (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - West Roxbury, MA, Jewish Cemetery, 1940s (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - West Roxbury, MA, Saint Theresa's, 1920s-1940s (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Westfield, MA, Saint Mary's Church, 1940s (Box 12, Folder 9-10)
  - Whitinsville, MA, Trinity Church, 1940s (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Wilmington, DE, Calvary Episcopal Church, 1950s (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Wilmington, DE, Trinity Church, 1950s (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Winchester, MA, First Congregational Church, 1940s (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Winchester, MA, Parish of the Epiphany, 1940s-1960s (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Winston Salem, NC, Saint Paul's Episcopal Church, 1940s-1960s (Box 12, Folder 16-19)
  - Winter Park, FL, Rollins College, Knowles Memorial Chapel, 1930s-1950s (Box 12, Folder 20-21)
  - Wollaston, MA, Wollaston Methodist Church, 1950s (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Woods Hole, MA, Church of the Messiah, 1950s (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Worcester, MA, All Saint's Church, 1930s-1970s (Box 12, Folder 24-27)
  - Worcester, MA, Central Congregational Church, 1950s (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Worcester, MA, Chestnut Street Congregational Church, 1940-1960s (Box 12, Folder 29-30)
  - Worcester, MA, Higgins, Mary, Residence, 1970s (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Worcester, MA, Johnson, Mrs. Herbert F., 1970s (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Worcester MA, Sacred Heart Church, 1940s (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Worcester, MA, State Mutual Life Assurance Company, 1950s (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Worcester, MA, Trinity Lutheran Church, 1950s (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - W, Miscellaneous, 1950s-1980s (Box 12, Folder 36-37)
  - Index Cards of Locations and Materials, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 42)
    index cards from Box 2, F36
- Financial Records, 1928-1982; Series 7; 1.14 Linear feet Boxes 13-14
  Financial records include general accounting and payroll records (restricted due to personal information), such as account books for project numbers 600s-700s, financial journals, purchase orders, bills and receipts, including those for work (primarily stained glass cabinet doors) supplied to the Gardner, Massachussetts furniture company Heywood-Wakefield Company in the 1970s, and orders submitted to glass suppliers S. A. Bendheim Co., Inc.
  Folders are arranged alphabetically by folder title.
  - Account Books, Project #s 600s, 1940s-1950s (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Account Books, Project #s 600s, 1950s (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Account Books, Project #s 600s-700s, 1950s (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Bills and Receipts, 1930s-1980s (Box 13, Folder 4-8)
  - Bills, Purchase Orders, Heywood-Wakefield Company, 1970s (Box 13, Folder 9-11)
  - Bills, S. A. Bendheim Co. Inc., 1928-1943 (Box 13, Folder 12-13)
  - Cash Book Fragments, 1970s (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Expense Reports, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Expenses/Receipts, 1960s-1970s (Box 13, Folder 16-17)
  - Financial Journal, 1961-1963 (Box 13, Folder 18-19)
  - Financial Journal, Payments and Receipts, 1962-1967 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Financial Journal, Payments and Receipts, 1968-1975 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Financial Journal, Loose Material found with Journal, 1956-1972 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Financial Journal, Repair Costs, 1959-1960s (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - General Ledger, 1963-1965 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Membership Dues, 1963-1966 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Payroll Books, 1968-1978 (Box 13, Folder 26-31)
  - Payroll Books, 1979; 1982 (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
  - Payroll Insurance, 1960s-1970 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Receipts, 1930s-1960 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Printed Material, circa 1920s-1980s; Series 8; 1.89 Linear feet Boxes 14-15, 27-28
  Printed material includes announcements and invitations for Burnham studio exhibitions; publications and news clippings about the Burnhams and their studio, and about stained glass in general; news clippings of source material; and news clippings about other subjects of interests to the Burnhams such as "Stained Glass, Contemporary Artists Work" and "Stained Glass, Modern Uses of."
  Material is arranged by type and is in rough chronological order thereafter.
  - Announcements and Invitations, circa 1920s-circa 1970s (Box 14, Folder 5-6)
  - Postcards, Blank, circa 1920s-circa 1970s (Box 14, Folder 7-8)
  - Publications and News Clippings, 1920s-1980s (Box 14, Folder 9-28)
  - Publications and News Clippings, 1970s-1980s (Box 15, Folder 1-3)
  - Source Material, circa 1920s-circa 1970s (Box 15, Folder 4-16)
    oversized material housed in Boxes 27-28
  - Source Material, Animals and Birds, circa 1930s-circa 1960s (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Source Material, Historical Costumes, circa 1930s-circa 1960s (Box 15, Folder 18-19)
  - Source Material, Sports, circa 1930s-circa 1960s (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - "Stained Glass, Contemporary Artists Work,", circa 1930s-circa 1960s (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - "Stained Glass, Modern Uses of,", circa 1930s-circa 1960s (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Oversized Publications and News Clippings, 1920s-1980s (Box 27)
    oversized material from Box 14, F 9-28
  - Oversized Source Material, circa 1920s-circa 1970s (Box 27)
    oversized material from Box 15, F 4-16
  - Oversized Source Material, circa 1920s-circa 1970s (Box 28)
- Scrapbooks, circa 1920s-circa 1970s; Series 9; 1.05 Linear feet Boxes 15-16, 28, OVs 48-49, BV 84
  Scrapbooks 1, 2 and 5, primarily contain news clippings in addition to invitations and announcements to Burnham Studios exhibitions and dedications of stained glass windows, and scattered phtotographs. Scrapbook 2 also contains clippings of artwork, primarily portraits and busts. Scrapbook 3 contains photographs of stained glass window art. Scrapbook 4 contains photographs of windows for the Church of Saint Vincent De Paul, Los Angeles, California. One folder contains scrapbook fragments from an unidentified source.
  The series also contains a 2 volume scrapbook, presumably compiled by Wilbur H. Burnham, Jr., related to a Pictorial Art course at Yale School of Fine Arts.
  - Scrapbook 1, 1941-1947 (Box 15, Folder 23-25)
  - Scrapbook 2, circa 1920s-circa 1940s (Box 15, Folder 26)
    oversized material housed in Box 28
  - Scrapbook 3, circa 1940s-circa 1970s (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Scrapbook 4, Los Angeles, CA, Church of Saint Vincent de Paul, circa 1940s-circa 1970s (Box 15, Folder 28)
    OV material housed in OVs 48-49
  - Scrapbook 5, circa 1920s-circa 1930s (Box 15, Folder 29)
    bound volume housed in BV 84
  - Scrapbook Fragments, 1930s-1940s (Box 15, Folder 30)
    OV material housed in Box 28
  - Yale School of Fine Arts, Pictorial Art Course Book, Part 1, circa 1930s (Box 15, Folder 31-34)
  - Yale School of Fine Arts, Pictorial Art Course Book, Part 2, circa 1930s (Box 16, Folder 1-6)
  - Oversized Scrapbook 2, circa 1920s-circa 1940s (Box 28)
    oversized material from Box 15, F 26
  - Oversized Scrapbook 3, circa 1940s-circa 1970s (Box 28)
    oversized material from Box 15, F 27
  - Oversized Scrapbook Fragments, 1930s-1940s (Box 28)
    oversized material from Box 15, F 30
  - Oversized Scrapbook 4, Los Angeles, CA, Church of Saint Vincent de Paul, circa 1940s-circa 1970s (Box OVs 48-49)
    oversized material from Box 15, F 28
  - Oversized Scrapbook 5, circa 1920s-circa 1930s (Box BV 84)
    bound volume fron Box 15, F 29
- Artwork and Sketchbooks, circa 1920s-circa 1980s; Series 10; 13.05 Linear feet Boxes 16-23, 29-39, OVs 50-73, 85 RD 83
  Artwork by Wilbur H. Burnham, Jr., includes pencil and ink sketches and paintings illustrating different styles for stained glass, such as Byzantine, Italian Rennaissance and French Gothic. Also found are a group of life sketches and some watercolors by Burnham, Jr.
  The bulk of the series consists of watercolor design studies on board for many of the studio's projects. Also found are stained glass design sketches and cartoons primarily in pencil and charcoal with scattered watercolors, as well as seven folders of material used for stained glass patterns and templates.
  Design studies on board are arranged in three groups. Studies numbered according to the "List of Numbered Contracts" from Series 5: Project Files, form the bulk of the material. A second group of studies is arranged according to a set of numbers for which no list or other cross-reference tool appears to exist. The third set of unnumbered studies is arranged at the end of the series. Some of the unnumbered studies have other identifying information indicating the location for which the design was created but they have not been arranged according to location.
  - Artwork by Wilbur H. Burnham, Jr., circa 1930s (Box 16, Folder 7-8)
    oversized material housed in Box 30, OV 50
  - Artwork by Wilbur H. Burnham, Jr., Life Sketches, circa 1930s; 1939 (Box 16, Folder 9-10)
    oversized material housed in OV 51-52
  - Artwork by Wilbur H. Burnham, Jr., Sketchbook, circa 1930s-circa 1940s (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Artwork by Unidentified Artists, circa 1930s-circa 1960s (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Christmas Greetings from Burnham Studios, circa 1920s-circa 1970s (Box 16, Folder 13-17)
  - Design Sketches and Cartoons, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 16, Folder 18)
    oversized material housed in Boxes 29-31, OV 83
  - Design Studies (Box 16)
    - Christmas Cards, circa 1930s (Box 16, Folder 19-21)
    - Framed Study with Broken Glass, circa 1940s (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Numbered, #1-157, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 16, Folder 23-29)
      oversized material housed in Box 32
    - Numbered, #203-570s, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 17, Folder 1-24)
      oversized material housed in Boxes 32-33, OVs 54-55
    - Numbered, #580s-682s, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 18, Folder 1-23)
      oversized material housed in Boxes 33-34, OV 55-57
    - Numbered, #683-727, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 19, Folder 1-23)
      oversized material housed in Box 34, OVs 57-58
    - Numbered, #728-770, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 20, Folder 1-21)
      oversized material housed in Boxes 34-35, OVs 59-60
    - Numbered, #773-913, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 21, Folder 1-10)
      oversized material housed in Box 35, OV 60
    - Numbered, Second Set, #1-290s, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 21, Folder 11-25)
      oversized material housed in Box 36
    - Numbered, Second Set, #300s-840s, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 22, Folder 1-25)
      oversized material housed in Boxes 36-37, OVs 61-65
    - Unnumbered, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 22, Folder 26-27)
      oversized material housed in Boxes 38-39, OVs 66-68
    - Unnumbered, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 23, Folder 1-14)
    - 3 Small Studies on Glass, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 23, Folder 16)
      oversized material housed in OVs 69-73
  - Patterns and Templates, circa 1920s-circa 1970s (Box 23, Folder 17)
    oversized material housed in Box 39
  - Patterns and Templates, #873, circa 1920s-circa 1970s (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Patterns and Templates, #874, circa 1920s-circa 1970s (Box 23, Folder 19-20)
  - Patterns and Templates, #875, circa 1920s-circa 1970s (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Patterns and Templates, Signs of the Zodiac, circa 1920s-circa 1970s (Box 23, Folder 22-23)
  - Oversized Design Sketches and Cartoons, Numbered #780, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 29)
    oversized material from Box 16, F 18
  - Oversized Artwork by Wilbur H. Burnham, Jr., circa 1930s (Box 30)
    oversized material from Box 16, F 7-8
  - Oversized Design Sketches and Cartoons, circa 1920s-circa 1970s (Box 30)
  - Oversized Design Sketches and Cartoons, circa 1920s-circa 1970s (Box 31)
  - Oversized Design Studies, Numbered 34-469, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 32)
    oversized material from Boxes 16-17
  - Oversized Design Studies, Numbered 472-623, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 33)
    oversized material from Boxes 17-18
  - Oversized Design Studies, Numbered 624-738, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 34)
    oversized material from Boxes 18-20
  - Oversized Design Studies, Numbered 749-786, 844, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 35)
    oversized material from Boxes 20-21
  - Oversized Design Studies, Numbered Second Set, 64, 301-599, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 36)
    oversized material from Boxes 21-22
  - Oversized Design Studies, Numbered Second Set, 601-809, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 37)
    oversized material from Box 22
  - Oversized Design Studies, Unnumbered, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 38)
    oversized material from Boxes 22-23
  - Oversized Design Studies, Unnumbered, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 39)
  - Oversized Patterns and Templates, circa 1920s-circa 1970s (Box 39)
    oversized material from Box 23
  - Oversized Artwork probably by Wilbur H. Burnham, Jr., circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box OV 50)
  - Oversized Artwork by Wilbur H. Burnham, Jr., Life Sketches, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box OV 51-52)
    oversized material from Box 16, F 9-10
  - Oversized Design Studies, Numbered, 158, 295, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box OV 53)
    oversized material from Box 17
  - Oversized Design Studies, Numbered, 307-491, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box OV 54)
  - Oversized Design Studies, Numbered, 505-587, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box OV 55)
  - Oversized Design Studies, Numbered, 608-634, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box OV 56)
    oversized material from Box 18
  - Oversized Design Studies, Numbered, 684-696, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box OV 57)
    oversized material from Box 19
  - Oversized Design Studies, Numbered, 719-726, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box OV 58)
  - Oversized Design Studies, Numbered, 729, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box OV 59)
    oversized material from Box 20
  - Oversized Design Studies, Numbered, 745-778, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box OV 60)
  - Oversized Design Studies, Numbered, Second Set, 673-725, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box OV 61)
  - Oversized Design Studies, Numbered, Second Set, 739-747, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box OV 62)
  - Oversized Design Studies, Numbered, Second Set, 754-769, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box OV 63)
  - Oversized Design Studies, Numbered, Second Set, 773-799, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box OV 64)
  - Oversized Design Studies, Numbered, Second Set, 804, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box OV 65)
  - Oversized Design Studies, Unnumbered, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box OV 66-68)
  - Oversized Design Studies, Miscellaneous, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box OV 69-73)
    oversized material from Box 23, F 16
  - Oversized Design Studies, Miscellaneous, circa 1920s-1980s (Box OV 85)
  - Oversized Cartoons, Saint John the Divine Designs Part 1, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box RD 83)
- Photographic Materials, circa 1904-circa 1980s; Series 11; 5.8 Linear feet Boxes 23-26, 29, 40-41, 43-47, OVs 74-82
  Found here are several photos of Wilbur H. Burnham, Sr. and Wilbur H. Burnham, Jr. and other studio staff, including three photographs of an office party. This series also provides a pictorial overview of the stained glass process through photos of people working on cartoons, and tracing, cutting, painting, firing, and glazing stained glass.
  One file includes 2 photos of window displays for an exhibition entitled "Christmas Themes in Stained Glass" with a collection of cards and labels.
  The bulk of the series consists of photos of stained glass cartoons and completed work. Also found are three sets of transparencies of artwork.
  Folders are arranged alphabetically by folder title. Photographs of artwork are arranged alphabetically by name of location, generally the town and state, in which the job site was located. The first two sets of transparencies are arranged by location and the third set is unidentified.
  - Photo of Cathedral Exteriors, circa 1950s (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Photos of Exhibition: "Christmas Themes in Stained Glass,", circa 1954-1955 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Photos of Office and Studio, circa 1930s-circa 1960s (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Photo of Stained Glass Association of America Dinner, circa 1950s (Box 23, Folder 27)
    oversized material housed in Box 40
  - Photos of Unidentified People, circa 1950s (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Photos of Wilbur H. Burnham, Jr., circa 1950s (Box 23, Folder 29)
    oversized material housed in Box 40, OV 74
  - Photos of Wilbur H. Burnham, Sr., circa 1920s-circa 1960s; circa 1904-circa 1906 (Box 23, Folder 30-31)
  - Photos of Work in Progress, circa 1950s (Box 23, Folder 32-35)
  - Photos of Artwork (Box 23)
    - A, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 23, Folder 36-37)
    - Blackford, James R., Designed and Drawn by, circa 1930s-1960s (Box 23, Folder 38)
      (includes photo of Blackford)
    - B, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 24, Folder 1-6)
    - C, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 24, Folder 7-13)
    - D, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - E, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 24, Folder 15-16)
    - F, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - G, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 24, Folder 18-19)
    - H, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 24, Folder 20-21)
    - K, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - L, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 24, Folder 23)
      oversized material housed in OV 75
    - M, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 24, Folder 24-25)
    - N, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 24, Folder 26-30)
      oversized material housed in Box 40, OV 75
    - O, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - P, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 25, Folder 1-6)
    - R, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - S, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 25, Folder 8-10)
      oversized material housed in Box 40, OV 76
    - T, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - W, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 25, Folder 12-23)
    - Unidentified/Miscellaneous, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 25, Folder 24-26)
      oversized material housed in Boxes 29, 41, OVs 77-82
    - Unidentified/Miscellaneous, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 26, Folder 1-17)
      OV material housed in Boxes 29, 41, OVs 77-82
  - Oversized Photographs of Artwork, Unidentified/Miscellaneous, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 29)
    oversized material from Box 25, F 24-26 and Box 26, F 1-17
  - Oversized Photograph of Stained Glass Association of America Dinner, circa 1950s (Box 40)
    oversized material from Box 23, F 27
  - Oversized Photographs of Wilbur H. Burnham, Jr. and Wilbur H. Burnham, Sr., 1954 (Box 40)
    oversized material from Box 23, F 29-31
  - Oversized Photographs of Work in Progress, circa 1950s (Box 40)
    oversized material from Box 23, F 32-35
  - Oversized Photographs of Artwork, A-C, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 40)
    oversized material from Box 23, F 36-Box 24, F 13
  - Oversized Photographs of Artwork, E, G, M, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 40)
    oversized material from Box 24, F 15-16, 18-19, 24-25
  - Oversized Photographs of Artwork, N, P, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 40)
    oversized material from Box 24, F 26-30, Box 25, F 1-6
  - Oversized Photographs of Artwork, S, T, W, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 40)
    oversized material from Box 25, F 8-23
  - Oversized Photographs of Artwork, Unidentified/Miscellaneous, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 41)
    oversized material from Box 25, F 24-26-Box 26, F 1-17
  - Photographs of Artwork, Transparencies (Box 43)
    - Set 1: Locations A-W, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 43)
    - Set 2: Locations A, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 43)
    - Set 2: Locations A-N, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 44)
    - Set 2: Locations N-W, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 45)
    - Set 3: Unidentified, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 45)
    - Set 3: Unidentified, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 46)
    - Set 3: Unidentified, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box 47)
  - Oversized Photograph of Wilbur H. Burnham, Sr. and Wilbur H. Burnham, Jr., 1954 (Box OV 74)
  - Oversized Photographs of Artwork, L, N, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box OV 75)
    oversized material from Box 24
  - Oversized Photographs of Artwork, S, W, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box OV 76)
    oversized material from Box 25
  - Oversized Photographs of Artwork, Unidentifed/Miscellaneous, circa 1920s-circa 1980s (Box OVs 77-82)